module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Which singer had a hit cover of Don McLean\'s "American Pie" in 2000?', 
    a: 'Tina Turner',
    b: 'Madonna',
    c: 'Mariah Carey',
    d: 'Cher',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country uses the krona as its currency?', 
    a: 'Australia',
    b: 'Morocco',
    c: 'Sweden',
    d: 'Brazil',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was Google\'s original name?', 
    a: 'BackRub',
    b: 'Lycos',
    c: 'Web Crawler',
    d: 'Excite',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: '"Bluetooth" wireless technology was named after what?', 
    a: 'A King',
    b: 'A Cat',
    c: 'A Crocodile',
    d: 'A Mountain',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the famous groundhog celebrated every year on February 2nd?', 
    a: 'Fred',
    b: 'Phil',
    c: 'Tom',
    d: 'Paul',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the softest type of wood?', 
    a: 'Hickory',
    b: 'Brazilian Walnut',
    c: 'Oak',
    d: 'Balsa',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What insect is often associated with Lyme Disease?', 
    a: 'Lice',
    b: 'Tick',
    c: 'Bed Bug',
    d: 'Mite',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was the father of Zeus?', 
    a: 'Poseidon',
    b: 'Atlas',
    c: 'Cronus',
    d: 'Calypso',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which popular dating app launched in 2012?', 
    a: 'Tinder',
    b: 'Bumble',
    c: 'Happn',
    d: 'Grindr',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which legendary character was responsible for leading children away from their homes in Germany?', 
    a: 'Rumpelstiltskin',
    b: 'Pied Piper',
    c: 'Grendel',
    d: 'Purzinigele',
    answer: 'b'
  },
];
